freelancewebmarket.com 2009-05-09

# Privacy-policy - FreelanceWebmarket

Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

This policy covers how FreelanceWebmarket.com treats personal information that FreelanceWebmarket.com collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and other information related you that is not otherwise publicly available except to provide products or services you have requested.  
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that FreelanceWebmarket.com does not own or control or to people that FreelanceWebmarket.com does not employ or manage.

FreelanceWebmarket.com collects personal information when you use FreelanceWebmarket.com products or services, when you register with FreelanceWebmarket.com, when you visit FreelanceWebmarket.com pages.  
When you register we ask for information such as your email address. For some financial products and services we might also ask for your address and information about your assets.   
FreelanceWebmarket.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.   
FreelanceWebmarket.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser.   
FreelanceWebmarket.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

FreelanceWebmarket.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you`ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:   
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with FreelanceWebmarket.com. These companies may use your personal information to help FreelanceWebmarket.com communicate with you about offers from FreelanceWebmarket.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.   
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of FreelanceWebmarket.com`s terms of use and conditions, or as otherwise required by law.   
We transfer information about you if FreelanceWebmarket.com is acquired by or merged with another company.

FreelanceWebmarket.com may set and access FreelanceWebmarket.com cookies on your computer.

You can edit your FreelanceWebmarket.com Account Information at any time.   
New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Account Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.   
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the FreelanceWebmarket.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the FreelanceWebmarket.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your FreelanceWebmarket.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.   
You can delete your FreelanceWebmarket.com account by contact us. We reserve the right to use your archived records after your account has been deleted.  

FreelanceWebmarket.com may amend or modify his Privacy Policy without notice, effective immediately, by updating this posting.

If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a contact form or you can contact us at:  

Sarkis Design OÜ  
Tammsaare tee 74-7  
Tallinn, 13413, Estonia  
Fax: (+372) 65 22 645  

or by email: [Contact Us](http://www.freelancewebmarket.com/contact.shtml?mod=Freelance_Projects)

Effective Date: January 07, 2007 (last update 26 07 2007)

FreelanceWebmarket offers an exciting professional environment where a diverse group of talented, experienced individuals work together as a team to build a new and exciting marketplace with a broad range of projects and services available to you at any time necessary. Our members are freelancers, companies and individuals from the United States, United Kingdom, Canada, India, Romania and many other countries. We provide you with an access to hundreds of qualified freelance, experienced and professionals. Service buyers will save time when searching for affordable and professional services from our network of professional programmers, developers, web designers etc., and service providers will save time when searching for gainful employment on the Internet. Our team has outstanding reputable professional and academic records and credentials, plus a passion for professional excellence and service to our members and partners. As a marketplace, FreelanceWebmarket is dedicated to ensuring that our workplace, culture, and benefits encourage all members to thrive both professionally and personally! We are constantly accepting résumés from dynamic, talented and highly motivated professional individuals as well as teams who strive to join our highly professional and progressive group, we offer a comprehensive equal-opportunity atmosphere that will surely be an asset to all who join. Custom web design projects, freelance work and outsourcing jobs on FreelanceWebmarket.
